CMD: "	I am ready are you"
Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "I'm ready.  What should we do next?"
CMD: "robot can I call you fido"
Robot: "Yes. I am Fido."
CMD: "please take a photo fido"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "fido take a photo every thirty degrees"
CMD: "and then go back to your starting position"
Robot: "I'm not sure what you mean by a photo every 30 degrees.  Should I turn around here 360 degrees?"
CMD: "start where you are and lurk until you are ninety degrees"
CMD: "then turn one eighty degrees"
CMD: "and then do another photo every thirty degrees until you're back to where your current position is"
CMD: "essentially I don't need photos behind you"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you go back to that blue sign on the wall back up to it"
CMD: "and take a photo"
CMD: "thank you fido"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "fido back up  to the other wall"
CMD: "and take a picture of that blue sign that's behind you"
Robot: "What other wall?  I see several walls."
CMD: "the wall on your right that's attached to the fire extinguisher"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "can you zoom in into that picture slash blue thing"
Robot: "I can't zoom in, but I can move closer, ok?"
CMD: "that's ok"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot do you read arabic"
Robot: "No.  Do you?"
CMD: "no I do not"
CMD: "can you go to the other doorway the one that's on your right"
CMD: "and go in about halfway into that room"
CMD: "turn left"
CMD: "then take a photo"
Robot: "How far should I turn left in the other room?"
CMD: "use your best judgement"
Robot: "I will turn 90 degrees when you say turn left, ok?"
CMD: "okay"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "turn left"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "do you know what that is"
CMD: "are you calibrated to detect shoes"
Robot: "No.  I need your help to find shoes."
CMD: "turn about thirty degrees"
CMD: "actually you know what take a photo of every corner in the room that you are currently in"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "turn around"
CMD: "and take another photo a closer look at those dvds or those boxes on top of the wood"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "can you go around and take a photo behind the tv"
CMD: "please and thank you"
Robot: "No.  My LIDAR map is showing no space behind the TV.  Do you want me to move around the left or right side of the TV?"
CMD: "no if you can just back up to the entryway of that room"
CMD: "take a photo"
CMD: "and then go into the other entryway on the left side of that room"
CMD: "and take a photo in front and behind you"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "nope stop stop"
CMD: "back up into that hallway"
Robot: "Did I misunderstand?"
Robot: "How far shoudl I back up?  Until I reach the wall behind me?"
CMD: "yes"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "turn to your right about ninety degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo"
CMD: "and turn a hundred and eighty degrees after that"
CMD: "and take another photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "investigate that white sign that's to your right"
Robot: "I see more than one white sign to my right.  Should I move to face the one closest to me?"
CMD: "please do"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
Robot: "Should I send a picture?"
CMD: "please"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "do you know what that is"
Robot: "I'm not sure, but it is similar to Arabic numerals."
CMD: "go into that room"
CMD: "and take a three hundred and sixty degree photo"
CMD: "actually you know what go into that room"
CMD: "go back to where you are"
CMD: "thanks fido"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "stop"
CMD: "go into the room you just saw"
Robot: "I'm not sure which room you are referring to.  Can you describe it another way, using proximity to an object or location?"
CMD: "how about you"
Robot: "I'm not sure what a doorway is exactly.  I detect six on the LIDAR map."
Robot: "I think you are more familiar with shoes than I am.  Good job finding them!"