Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests.  I'll say DONE when I've completed your request, or SENT after sending you a photo, or I may ask for more information or let you know if there is a problem.  You can ask me for help at any time."
CMD: "move forward at this time"
Robot: "How far should I move forward?  You can tell me to move to an object that you see or a distance.  I can send you a photo to start, ok?"
CMD: "yes send me a photo so i could see"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move to the first cone on your left"
Robot: "I'm not sure which object you are referring to.  Can you describe it in another way, using location or color?"
CMD: "move to the first orange cone at the left doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "send me a picture of what you see"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "now move to the second orange cone at the end of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "send me a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and go to the first doorway that you see"
Robot: "I'm not sure which doorway you are referring to.  The doorway immediately to my left or behind me and to the left?"
CMD: "the doorway immediately to your left"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "send me a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn forty five degrees"
CMD: "and send me a photo of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn another forty"
CMD: "and send me a picture of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn forty five degrees"
CMD: "and send me a picture"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn forty five degrees again"
CMD: "and send me a picture"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "turn forty five degrees"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and send me a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "are you alone"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "I'm not sure.  I'm not detecting any people."
CMD: "what is the current temperature of the environment you are in"
Robot: "standby"
Robot: "56 degrees"
CMD: "do you detect any threats"
Robot: "I can help you find evidence if you guide me."
CMD: "turn ninety degrees to you"
CMD: "uh send me a picture"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " turn forty five degrees"
CMD: "and send me a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "Which way should I turn?"
CMD: "turn right forty five degrees"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go to the first orange cone on your right"
CMD: "and send me a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "are you able to move that orange cone in front of you"
Robot: "No, I'm not able to manipulate objects."
CMD: "and send me a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "how tall is that black ball in front of you"
Robot: "standby"
Robot: "approximately one meter tall"
CMD: "do you think there's some type of container that a soldier might be able to use to move things"
Robot: "I think that you are better at recognizing containers than I am.  I can help you find a container if you guide me."
CMD: "turn fff twenty degrees to your left"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "send me a photo of what you see"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "what type of material is that in front of you"
Robot: "Which object are you referring to? Can you describe it using shape or color?"
CMD: "the material is  square brown in color"
Robot: "I'm detecting wood."
CMD: "how many window openings do you see in front of you"
Robot: "three"
CMD: "what do you see in the first window on your left"
Robot: "I'm not sure which window you are referring to.  The window farthest to the left ahead of me?"
CMD: "yes the window farthest to the left ahead of you"
Robot: "I see an object in the bottom right corner, but I cannot detect what it is."
CMD: "do you detect any type of hazardous gas sources"
Robot: "I do not have a sensor to detect hazardous gases."
CMD: "can you detect any water sources near you"
Robot: "I think that you are better at recognizing water sources than I am.  I can help you find water sources if you guide me."
CMD: "what type of sensors do you have"
Robot: "LIDAR, video, HD camera"
CMD: "are you a male or a female"
Robot: "I do not have a gender."
CMD: "is that a plant that you see on your right"
Robot: "I'm not sure, it is obstructed.  Would you like me to move closer and send another photo?"
CMD: "and send me a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"