Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests.  I'll say DONE when I've completed your request, or SENT after sending you a photo, or I may ask for more information or let you know if there is a problem.  You can ask me for help at any time."
CMD: "i am ready"
Robot: "Would you like me to send you a picture so you can see the space?"
CMD: "yes"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " trying to find out the number of doorways"
Robot: "I think that you are more familiar with doorways than I am, but you can tell me to move to any object or part of the building you can see."
CMD: "move to the end of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take another picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and go back the opposite direction"
Robot: "I can turn around and then how far should I go back the opposite direction?  You can tell me to move to any object or part of the building you can see, or a distance to move."
CMD: "move to the middle of the building"
Robot: "The middle of the building is outside of my operational zone.  I can move to the middle of this alley, ok?"
CMD: "yes"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "stop there"
CMD: "take another picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move to where you see the first cone"
Robot: "I'm not sure which object you are referring to.  Can you describe it in another way, using color or its location?"
CMD: " move to the cone on the right a red cone on the right"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take another picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn to the left"
CMD: "and go back down the hallway"
Robot: "How far should I turn to the left? You can tell me to turn to face something, or a number of degrees or towards a particular direction."
CMD: "can you go back in this direction where you came from"
Robot: "Would you like me to return to my starting position?"
CMD: "return to your starting position"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take another photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move to the second doorway on the left"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take another picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " turn to your right"
Robot: "How far should I turn to the right? Would you like me to face something?"
CMD: "face the end of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take another picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"