CMD: "robot turn one hundred and eighty degrees"
CMD: "and proceed  one two three four five"
CMD: "uh cancel last request uh robot"
CMD: "turn one hundred and eighty degrees"
CMD: "and proceed  one meter"
CMD: "robot proceed three meters"
CMD: "robot proceed ten meters"
CMD: "robot take a photo"
Robot: "calibration complete"
CMD: "robot turn ninety degrees left"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot turn forty five degrees right"
CMD: "and continue to second doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot stop"
CMD: "robot take a photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "Please be patient.  I'm experiencing some technical issues."
CMD: "robot take a photo"
CMD: "robot turn ninety degrees to the left"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot continue to the first doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot take a photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot turn ninety degrees to the left"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "and take a photo"
CMD: "robot confirm that the object in front of you is a ladder"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "I think that you are more familiar with ladders than I am.  Would you like me to move back from this object to get another photo?"
CMD: "robot turn a hundred and eight degrees"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot proceed to the other doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot take a photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"