Robot: "calibration complete"
CMD: "i am ready"
Robot: "I'm ready too.  Would you like me to send a picture so you can see the space?"
CMD: "yes"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move through the doorway"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "There is a doorway directly in front of me and one to the left of me.  Which should I move through?"
CMD: "move through the doorway directly in front of you"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "do a three hundred and sixty degree turn"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "send a picture"
CMD: "turn around and face the door that you just came into"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move closer to the door towards the fire extinguisher"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "About how much closer should I get?"
CMD: "about three feet"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " move closer to the fire extinguisher"
Robot: "Three feet closer?"
CMD: "take a picture "
CMD: "yes"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn around"
CMD: "and go back out of the door that you came into"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go back out of the door that you came into"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn to your right"
CMD: "and go down the hallway"
Robot: "I'm not sure what hallway you are referring to.  I can turn to my right and go through the door to my right, ok?"
CMD: "go through the doorway to your right"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "continue to move down the hallway"
Robot: "How far should I continue down the hallway? Would you like me to reach something that you see or go a certain distance?"
CMD: "go down the end of the hallway where it appears to be a clock on the wall"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn back around"
CMD: "and go  towards the dis uh my sign is saying"
CMD: "turn back around and "
CMD: "go back down the end of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "make a right"
CMD: "and keep straight"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "How far should I turn right?"
CMD: "change of command"
CMD: "turn back around"
CMD: "and go back down the end of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "make a right"
CMD: "turn back around"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "and make a  go in the first left the first doorway to your left"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go further inside the doorway to your left"
Robot: "About how far should I go to the left? Three feet?"
CMD: "about  four feet"
CMD: "about four feet to your left"
CMD: "make a right  well about three feet"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "and a quick left"
Robot: "How far should I turn to the right?"
CMD: "three feet"
CMD: "go through the doorway that's inside of the room"
Robot: "I'm not sure how to turn to the right three feet.  You can tell me to rotate to face something, or a number of degrees, or to a certain direction."
Robot: "The doorway to my right?"
CMD: "yes"
CMD: "the doorway to your right"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go back out of the doorway you entered into"
CMD: "and go back down the hallway to the left"
Robot: "About how far down the hallway should I go?"
CMD: "all the way to the end of the hallway "
Robot: "To the end of the hallway?"
CMD: "and make a right"
CMD: "yes"
Robot: "How far should I turn right once I get to the end of the hallway?"
CMD: "move to the end of the hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"