Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot turn a hundred eighty degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot turn one hundred and eighty degrees"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " and proceed through the doorway about one foot into the room"
CMD: "then take a photo"
Robot: "I'm not sure which doorway you mean?"
CMD: "robot turn one hundred and eighty degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot proceed two meters"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn ninety degrees to the right"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot turn ninety degrees to the left"
CMD: "and continue to the farther wall"
Robot: "I'm not sure what you mean by the farther wall.  Where should I continue to?"
CMD: "robot continue down the hallway directly in front of you underneath the overhead light"
Robot: "I don't see an overhead light in my current position.  Would you like me to send a photo?"
CMD: "robot send a photo"
CMD: "robot continue  moving forward to the right of the red bucket"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and continue forward until you reach the wall"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot turn ninety degrees left"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot continue forward"
CMD: "and take a photo of the item hanging off the desk"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot turn ninety degrees to the left"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot continue further"
CMD: "and take a photo of the map on the wall"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot return to the main hallway"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "robot take a photo"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot continue to the second doorway in the hallway"
CMD: "turn left ninety degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot take a photo of the poster on the wall"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "PLease be patient, I'm experiencing technical issues."
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "system"
CMD: "uh recalibrate"
Robot: "calibrating..."
Robot: "calibration complete"
CMD: "robot turn ninety degrees right"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot proceed to the middle of the room in front of you"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "then turn ninety degrees right"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "I'm not sure which room you mean.  Should I proceed to the middle of this room or the next room?"
CMD: "robot proceed to the middle of the next room"
CMD: "turn ninety degrees right"
CMD: "and then take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot enter the hallway through the door thirty five degrees to your right and in front of you "
CMD: "then face left in the hallway"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "I'm not sure what you mean by face left?"
CMD: " robot exit the doorway in front of you moving into the main hall"
CMD: "robot turn forty five degrees left"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot turn forty five  degrees left"
CMD: "and take a photo "
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sente"
CMD: "robot continue down this hallway to the next doorway on the left"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot  turn nine  robot turn ninety degrees left"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot take a photo of the cereal box on the desk"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "robot turn a hundred and eighty degrees"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot continue through the doorway in front of you"
CMD: "turn ninety degrees right"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot continue into the hallway here"
Robot: "How far should I continue into the hallway?"
CMD: "robot continue into the beginning of the hallway"
CMD: "then face north"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"