Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests.  I'll say DONE when I've completed your request, or SENT after sending you a photo, or I may ask for more information or let you know if there is a problem.  You can ask me for help at any time."
CMD: "take a photo"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "I'm ready"
CMD: "move forward a little bit"
Robot: "I'm also ready.  What should I do next?  You can tell me to move to an object that you see or to move a certain distance."
Robot: "How far is a little bit?"
CMD: "two feet"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "and then turn left"
CMD: "then take a photo"
Robot: "Does a little bit mean two feet?"
CMD: "yes it does"
Robot: "How far should I turn left?  Until facing the door to my left?"
CMD: "perpendicular to the doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a photo"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move around the cone into the next room"
CMD: "turn right ninety degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "There is not enough space for me to move around the cone and enter the room ahead.  Would you like me to get as close as possible to the room?"
CMD: "on the right side of the cone"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "turn left about forty five degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "can you tell if there's a doorway in that room"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "My LIDAR map isn't showing any other doorway in the room ahead."
CMD: "then turn around one hundred and eighty degrees"
CMD: "move forward about two feet"
CMD: "then turn left and continue down the hallway you're in"
Robot: "How far should I continue down the hallway?"
CMD: "continue up to the next opening on your left side"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and then can you tell what is inside that doorway"
Robot: "You are probably more familiar with the objects inside the doorway than I am.  Should I send a picture after turning to face the doorway?"
CMD: "yes"
CMD: "can you get around that object"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "No, the object is obstructing the doorway."
CMD: "turn to your left ninety degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go back to the other doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "face the doorway"
CMD: "and back up until you hit the wall"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "or just about hit the wall"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "stop"
CMD: "take a photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "do the same thing to the other doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "move up to that  space between the uh object that blocks the doorway in the doorway itself"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and take another photo so i have a clear picture of everything"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go back to where you started"
CMD: "turn a hundred and eighty degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo at the entryway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "back up a little bit"
Robot: "How far is a little bit?"
CMD: "same thing as before by two feet"
Robot: "Two feet?"
CMD: "you know what make it four"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a photo"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "are you sure there's no way to get into the first doorway"
Robot: "I'm not sure.  I will return to face the first doorway and send a photo, ok?"
CMD: "no just back up a little bit"
CMD: "and take another photo"
Robot: "Four feet?"
CMD: "two feet this time"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go back to the start"
CMD: "and turn around"
CMD: "and do a victory lap"
CMD: "i saw two cones how about you robot"
Robot: "I think you are better at recognizing cones than I am."