Robot: "calibration complete"
CMD: "aight  robot let's do this"
Robot: "I'm ready.  What should we do know?"
CMD: "start by turning left ninety degrees"
CMD: "and take a photo until you are at your current position"
CMD: "take a photo every thirty degrees until you are at your current position"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "can you go into the center of that room"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "and take a photo uh every thirty degrees"
CMD: "doing a three hundred and sixty degree perimeter"
Robot: "The center of which room?"
CMD: "the room that you're currently in"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "wait"
Robot: "Could you please repeat that?"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "go back to that yellow cone"
CMD: "and take a photo close to the black image"
Robot: "I'm not sure what you are referring to, but I'll move to face the yellow cone and send a picture, ok?"
CMD: "okay"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot go to that white sign that's in the picture"
CMD: "and take a picture of it"
CMD: "also do you speak any other languages"
Robot: "I do not speak.  I can recognize some English words."
CMD: "go to the end of the hallway that is to your right"
CMD: "and take a picture of the white sign that's on the doorway or on the uh wall"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "are those arabic numbers"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "I'm not sure.  We have seen something similar here.  What do you think?"
CMD: "er in front of you i mean"
Robot: "Would you like photos every 30 degrees?"
CMD: "yes please"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "uh there is a white door and a red sign"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture of the red sign"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn to the left to face the rest of the room"
CMD: "and take a picture"
Robot: "Should I turn left 180 degrees?"
CMD: "a few degrees less than that"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "turn right about thirty degrees"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "and take a picture"
CMD: "then go into that hallway slash room"
CMD: "and go up against the wall that's on your right"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "I'm not sure which room you are referring to.  The room through the doorway to the right?"
CMD: "thank you"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "what's that object just to the left of the photo"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "if you can't tell me go over to it"
CMD: "and take a picture but keep the rest of the room in focus"
Robot: "I'm not sure.  I will turn to face it and send a photo."
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "send"
CMD: "are you able to tip over that bag"
Robot: "Could you repeat that?"
CMD: "are you able to knock over or tip over that object"
CMD: "go into the hallway that is uh ahead of you"
Robot: "I cannot manipulate objects in the environment without jeopardizing my safety.  Should I get closer?"
CMD: "go into the hallway that's uh in front of you to your right"
CMD: "and then make a ninety degree right"
CMD: "and then go into the right room"
CMD: "take a picture every thirty degrees three hundred and sixty degrees in the room in the center of the room"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "what's that white sign in the room on your left"
Robot: "I'm not sure what you are referring to.  Can you describe it another way, using proximity to me or another object?"
CMD: "go to the doorway that is on your left"
CMD: "about thirty degrees and face it into the unknown area"
CMD: "and take a picture into it"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "have we been here"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "yes"
CMD: "robot go back to the start"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "what was that"
Robot: "I miscalculated and hit a wall."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "go forward about ten feet"
CMD: "make a right"
CMD: "and go into the hallway we haven't explored uh on the would be your right side"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "go back about three feet"
CMD: "and then thirty degrees to your right again"
CMD: "and take a photo"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "sent"