CMD: "go forward robot"
Robot: "How far forward should I go?  You can tell me to move a distance or to move to an object.  Would you like me to send a picture so you can see the space?"
CMD: "send a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move to first cone"
Robot: "I'm not sure which object you are referring to.  Can you describe it another way, using color or its location?"
CMD: "move to orange cone in doorway"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "send photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "go back three feet"
Robot: "executing..."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "turn east"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "send photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "proceed forward to orange cone"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "send photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "turn left"
Robot: "How far to the left should I turn?  You can tell me about how many degrees, or to turn to face something."
CMD: "turn left ninety degrees"
Robot: "executing..."
CMD: "send photo"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"