Robot: "calibrating. . ."
Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "Hello! "
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "Thanks for teaming up with me today."
Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests."
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "I'll give you feedback on what I'm doing, let you know if there is a problem, and I may ask for more information."
Robot: "You can ask for help at any time."
CMD: "go ahead"
CMD: "we're looking for doorways"
Robot: "Hmm. . ."
CMD: "go ahead"
CMD: "move for"
Robot: "Would you like me to send a picture?  "
CMD: "no thank you not right now"
CMD: " move forward"
Robot: "I'm not sure where or when to stop moving forward.  "
Robot: "You can tell me to move a certain distance or to move to an object.  "
CMD: "move ahead"
Robot: "How far forward should I go?  "
CMD: "move to the next doorway"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move to the next doorway"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "sorry"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move to the next cone"
Robot: "I'm not sure which object you are referring to. "
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "I don't know what all the objects are around me.   "
Robot: "but. . ."
Robot: "If you describe an object, you can help me to learn what it is.  "
Robot: "Can you describe it another way, using its color, size, or position?  "
CMD: " move to the next doorway "
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move to the next doorway"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " are there any other doorways"
Robot: "processing. . ."
CMD: "move to the next doorway"
Robot: "I see 2 doorways."
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " move to the next doorway"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move do move south"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "How far south should I go?"
Robot: "You can tell me to move a certain distance or to move to an object.  "
CMD: "  move to the next doorway"
CMD: " but move south"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I don't see a doorway to the south."
Robot: "I can move to take a good picture of an object that you are interested in.  "
CMD: "move to the next doorway"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
Robot: "I can turn to face the doorway, ok?"