Robot: "calibrating. . ."
Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "Hello! "
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "Thanks for teaming up with me today."
Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests."
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "I'll give you feedback on what I'm doing, let you know if there is a problem, and I may ask for more information."
Robot: "You can ask for help at any time."
CMD: "travel straight"
Robot: "I'm not sure where or when to stop moving forward.  "
Robot: "You can tell me to move a certain distance or to move to an object.  "
CMD: "um travel east two feet"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "travel east two more feet"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "moving. . ."
CMD: " turn to the left"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "and take a picture"
Robot: "I'm unsure where or when I should stop turning.  "
Robot: "You can tell me to turn a number of degrees or to face something.  "
CMD: "turn north thirty degrees"
CMD: "and take a picture"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "turn east thirty degrees"
CMD: "and travel  five feet"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "turn south ninety degrees"
CMD: "and take a picture"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: " turn east ninety degrees"
CMD: "and travel three feet"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: " turn north forty five degrees"
CMD: "and take picture"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: " turn east"
CMD: "and travel five feet"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: " turn to the right fifteen degrees"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "  turn to the left uh fifteen degrees"
CMD: "travel three feet"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "make sure i didn't miss something"
CMD: " turn one hundred and eighty degrees"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "I will turn around 180 degrees"
Robot: "turning. . ."
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " turn left"
CMD: "and take a picture"
Robot: "How far should I turn to the left?  "
CMD: "fifteen degrees"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "  turn fifteen degrees to your right>"
CMD: "and travel eight feet"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "travel three feet "
CMD: "turn fifteen degrees to your right"
CMD: "and take a picture"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I will move forward 3 feet"
Robot: "and. . ."
Robot: "I will turn right 15 degrees"
Robot: "I will send a picture"
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: " turn left left fifteen degrees"
CMD: "travel four feet"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "turn right fifteen degrees"
CMD: "t take a picture"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"