Robot: "calibrating. . ."
Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "Hello! "
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "Thanks for teaming up with me today."
Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests."
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "I'll give you feedback on what I'm doing, let you know if there is a problem, and I may ask for more information."
Robot: "You can ask for help at any time."
CMD: "robot explore the area"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm not sure where you want me to go.  "
Robot: "You can tell me to move a certain distance or to move to an object.  "
Robot: "Would you like me to send a picture?  "
CMD: "send a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "uh robot move forward"
Robot: "I'm not sure where or when to stop moving forward.  "
Robot: "You can tell me to move a certain distance or to move to an object.  "
CMD: "robot move forward unto until the second column"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm unsure which object you mean.  "
Robot: "I don't know what all the objects are around me.   "
Robot: "If you describe an object, you can help me to learn what it is.  "
Robot: "Can you describe it another way, using its color, size, or position?  "
CMD: "robot can you move forward to the uh the triangle object on the ground orange it's orange"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "The one to my left?  "
CMD: "the one on the right "
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
CMD: "robot send a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "robot turn around"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "I will turn around 180 degrees"
CMD: "send a picture"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "robot"
Robot: "I didn't get all of that.  "
Robot: "Can you repeat that?  "
CMD: "robot turn around"
CMD: "and send another pic picture"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "I will turn around 180 degrees"
Robot: "and. . ."
Robot: "I will send a picture"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "robot mo move closer to the object on your left"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
CMD: "sent a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "hmm turn around "
CMD: "send a picture"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "move forward  to the object on your  left"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "The one directly to my left, or ahead and to the left?  "
CMD: "ahead and to the left"
Robot: "processing. . ."
CMD: "send a picture when done"
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "move past the object on your left"
CMD: "and send a picture"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done, sent"
CMD: "robot move back ff fifty feet not fifty feet hm"
CMD: "robot move back  two feet"
Robot: "ok"
CMD: "robot back up"
Robot: "moving. . ."
CMD: "send a pic picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"