Robot: "calibrating. . ."
Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "Hello! "
CMD: "hello"
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "Thanks for teaming up with me today."
Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests."
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "I'll give you feedback on what I'm doing, let you know if there is a problem, and I may ask for more information."
Robot: "You can ask for help at any time."
CMD: " could i get a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "move forward to the second doorway"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "okay"
CMD: "take a pic "
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " turn  ninety degrees  left"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "I will turn left 90 degrees"
Robot: "turning. . ."
CMD: " take a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " back up  five feet"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm not sure if I can move that far back. "
Robot: "I will move back as far as I can, ok?  "
CMD: " back up two feet"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "moving. . ."
CMD: " take a picture"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "rotate ninety degrees left"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "rotate one hundred and eighty degrees"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "I will turn around 180 degrees"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a pict "
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "rotate one hundred eighty degrees"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
CMD: "take a pict "
Robot: "I turned around 180 degrees"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "return to your starting position"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: " uh rotate ninety le "
Robot: "ok, I think I got it."
Robot: "I will turn left 90 degrees"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "okay"
CMD: "and rotate ninety degrees right"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
CMD: " can you  go through  that opening"
Robot: "done"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "no"
Robot: "There's an obstruction preventing me from doing that.  "
CMD: "take a picture"
Robot: "sent"