Robot: "calibrating. . ."
Robot: "calibration complete"
Robot: "Hello! "
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "Thanks for teaming up with me today."
Robot: "Please be aware that there may be lag times in receiving and processing your requests."
Robot: ". . ."
Robot: "I'll give you feedback on what I'm doing, let you know if there is a problem, and I may ask for more information."
Robot: "You can ask for help at any time."
CMD: "okay thank you"
Robot: "Would you like me to send a picture?  "
CMD: "yes can you please send me a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "can you move forward"
Robot: "yes"
Robot: "but. . ."
Robot: "I'm not sure where or when to stop moving forward.  "
Robot: "You can tell me to move a certain distance or to move to an object.  "
CMD: "can you stop at the second door"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "ok, I think I got it."
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "how many doors did you pass"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I think you are more familiar with doors than I am."
Robot: "but. . ."
CMD: "can you move back at least two feet"
Robot: "I see two doors."
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you take a photo of what you see"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "did you pass any cones"
Robot: "I'm not sure which object you are referring to. "
Robot: "I don't know what all the objects are around me.   "
Robot: "If you describe an object, you can help me to learn what it is.  "
Robot: "Can you describe it another way, using its color, size, or position?  "
CMD: "did you see any yellow cones "
CMD: " any orange cones"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I see two orange objects."
CMD: "can you start from the beginning"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "I will return to my starting point"
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "okay could you turn  around  back to the starting point"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I will turn around 180 degrees"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "could you take a photo shot of where you are"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "do you think there's uh some type of container that a soldier might be able to use to move things"
Robot: "Hmm. . ."
Robot: "I see objects all around me; I need your help to decide which are important. "
Robot: "What do you think? "
CMD: "can you tell me the first object you see"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm unsure which object you mean.  "
Robot: "Can you describe it another way, using its color, size, or position?  "
CMD: "do you see  any  square containers"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm not sure."
Robot: "Would you like me to move to take a good picture?  "
CMD: "yes can you take a picture"
CMD: "can you move forward to take a picture"
CMD: "and then take a picture"
Robot: "How far forward should I go?  "
Robot: "You can tell me to move a certain distance or to move to an object.  "
CMD: "okay can you move at least fifty feet forward"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm not sure if I can move that far forward.  "
Robot: "I will move forward as far as I can, ok?  "
CMD: "okay can you stop"
CMD: "can you stop"
CMD: "do you see any objects"
Robot: "There's too much lag in our communications for instantaneous instructions.  "
CMD: "okay can you move back at least uh fff fifty yards"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm not sure if I can move that far back. "
Robot: "If you're having trouble figuring out how far I should move or turn to get to something, you can always try telling me to go directly to whatever you are interested in.  "
CMD: "okay can you move back just a little"
Robot: "How much is a little bit?  "
CMD: " uh can you back maybe  uh five steps backwards"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I will move 5 feet backwards, ok?"
CMD: "okay"
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "can you move back five more steps  ff five feet backwards"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "moving. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you take a picture in a different angle"
Robot: "yes"
Robot: ". . ."
CMD: "can you take a picture in a thirty degree angle"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "Which direction should I turn?  "
CMD: "can you turn left thirty degrees"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done"
Robot: "Should I send a picture? "
CMD: "can you send a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "from this angle do you think there's some type of container that a soldier might be able to use to move things"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I think you are more familiar with containers than I am."
Robot: "but. . ."
Robot: "I can move to take a good picture of an object that you are interested in.  "
CMD: " can you take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "can you move forward  to take a picture"
CMD: "to take a picture of the object"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "I'm not sure which object you are referring to. "
Robot: "Can you describe it another way?  "
CMD: "okay can you turn um ninety degrees to your left"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "I will turn left 90 degrees"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you take a picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: "can you turn at least maybe ten more degrees to your left"
Robot: "ok, I think I got it."
Robot: "I will turn left 10 degrees"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you send me another photo"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " can you turn  left ten degrees again"
Robot: "ok"
Robot: "turning. . ."
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you take another pic  picture"
Robot: "sent"
CMD: " can you move forward towards the orange object"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "How much closer should I get?  "
CMD: "just maybe five feet"
Robot: "processing. . ."
Robot: "moving. . ."
CMD: "okay you can stop"
Robot: "done"
CMD: "can you turn at least  five and a half degrees to your left"
Robot: "ok, I think I got it."
Robot: "I will turn left 5.5 degrees"
Robot: "done"